- ObjectiveID: C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: C91_container_00_FQ_01
  NpcDestinationId: Fish_Perronelle
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: C91_FishQ_01
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_FishingPole_FishQuestT1
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_title"
  Description: "@C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@C91_FQ_01_UnpathedWaters_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: FishingQuestsArc
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: C91_container_00_FQ_02
  NpcDestinationId: Fish_Perronelle
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: C91_FishQ_02
  RequiredAchievementId: C91_FishQ_01
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_title"
  Description: "@C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@C91_FQ_02_UndreamedShores_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: FishingQuestsArc
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: C91_FQ_02_Vector
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: C91_FQ_02_Vector_Container
  NpcDestinationId: Fish_Khadijah
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: C91_FQ_02_Vector
  RequiredAchievementId: C91_FishQ_02
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: C91_FQ_02_Vector_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@C91_FQ_02_Vector_title"
  Description: "@C91_FQ_02_Vector_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@C91_FQ_02_Vector_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@C91_FQ_02_Vector_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@C91_FQ_02_Vector_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@C91_FQ_02_Vector_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: FishingQuestsArc
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: C91_container_00_FQ_03
  NpcDestinationId: Fish_Khadijah
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: C91_FishQ_03
  RequiredAchievementId: C91_FQ_02_Vector
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_title"
  Description: "@C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@C91_FQ_03_DeboshedFish_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: FishingQuestsArc
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: C91_FQ_03_Vector
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: C91_FQ_03_Vector_Container
  NpcDestinationId: Fish_Ishikawa
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: C91_FQ_03_Vector
  RequiredAchievementId: C91_FishQ_03
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: C91_FQ_03_Vector_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@C91_FQ_03_Vector_title"
  Description: "@C91_FQ_03_Vector_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@C91_FQ_03_Vector_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@C91_FQ_03_Vector_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@C91_FQ_03_Vector_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@C91_FQ_03_Vector_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: FishingQuestsArc
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: C91_container_00_FQ_04
  NpcDestinationId: Fish_Ishikawa
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: C91_FishQ_04
  RequiredAchievementId: C91_FQ_03_Vector
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: BaitFishT3
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_title"
  Description: "@C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@C91_FQ_04_MelancholyBait_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: FishingQuestsArc
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: C91_container_00_FQ_05
  NpcDestinationId: Fish_Ishikawa
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: C91_FishQ_05
  RequiredAchievementId: C91_FishQ_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_title"
  Description: "@C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@C91_FQ_05_GildedTombs_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: FishingQuestsArc
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: C91_FQ_05_Vector
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: C91_FQ_05_Vector_Container
  NpcDestinationId: Fish_Khadijah
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: C91_FQ_05_Vector
  RequiredAchievementId: C91_FishQ_05
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: C91_FQ_05_Vector_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@C91_FQ_05_Vector_title"
  Description: "@C91_FQ_05_Vector_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@C91_FQ_05_Vector_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@C91_FQ_05_Vector_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@C91_FQ_05_Vector_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@C91_FQ_05_Vector_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: FishingQuestsArc
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: C91_FQ_06_RotsHead
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: C91_container_00_FQ_06
  NpcDestinationId: Fish_Khadijah
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: C91_FishQ_06
  RequiredAchievementId: C91_FQ_05_Vector
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_RotsHead_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_title"
  Description: "@C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@C91_FQ_06_RotsHead_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: FishingQuestsArc
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: C91_FQ_06_Vector
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: C91_FQ_06_Vector_Container
  NpcDestinationId: Fish_Perronelle_C
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: C91_FQ_06_Vector
  RequiredAchievementId: C91_FishQ_06
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: C91_FQ_06_Vector_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@C91_FQ_06_Vector_title"
  Description: "@C91_FQ_06_Vector_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@C91_FQ_06_Vector_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@C91_FQ_06_Vector_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@C91_FQ_06_Vector_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@C91_FQ_06_Vector_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: FishingQuestsArc
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: C91_container_00_FQ_07
  NpcDestinationId: Fish_Pelles_A
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: C91_FishQ_07
  RequiredAchievementId: C91_FQ_06_Vector
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_title"
  Description: "@C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@C91_FQ_07_DepthsClose_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: FishingQuestsArc
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: C91_FQ_08_FisherKing
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: C91_container_00_FQ_08
  NpcDestinationId: Fish_Perronelle_C
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: C91_FishQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: C91_FishQ_07
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_title"
  Description: "@C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@C91_FQ_08_FisherKing_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: FishingQuestsArc
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
